<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<Configuration>
	<Options>						
		<Option key="STORY#LEVEL2#0">Unlike nowdays, many centuries ago the worlds of dreams and nightmares were two places completely different from each other. An indestructible, ethereal veil was responsible for keeping both oneiric worlds separate, and there was no way to cross the veil from one realm to the opposite.\n\n
		This prevented the foul inhabitants of the nightmares realms from stepping into the world of dreams and terrorizing both the dreamers and the world's dwellers, particularly one of their kings, who was as easily frightened as he was good-natured.\n\n
		Meanwhile, in the real world a reputed inventor, whose real name has got lost in the drifts of time, but who's been known as the Watchmaker ever since, came up with an amazing device: a magic clock with the ability of teleporting its owner to the Dream world while at the same time she could retain full consciousness. What's more, she also became able to materialize some magical contraptions from the most hidden corners of her subconscious mind.\n\n
		The Watchmaker then began exploring the world of dreams, meeting most of its inhabitants. However, as the king quickly noticed, these travels came at a price...
		</Option>
		<Option key="STORY#LEVEL2#1">
		Any time that the magical clock was used the veil became thinner. Terrified by the implications, the king urged the Watchmaker to destroy the device. Too enthralled with his own invention, though, he paid no heed to the warnings until the inevitable happened and the Veil was torn. Instantly, hundreds of monsters from the nightmares world appeared in the land of dreams and started to wreak havoc everywhere.\n\n One of their leaders was a huge, bird-like monster who, commanding an army of similar creatures, invaded the dominions of the king from our story, overthrowing him. No news of the king have been heard so far, so he was feared kidnapped or worse. Feeling guilty, the Watchmaker attempted to make amends: he designed a set of spheres, located  at the spots where the Veil had been ripped open,acting like a patch to keep the shreds together.\n\n 
		In the end, the Watchmaker redeemed himself and went back to the conscious world vowing never to return. The two worlds were separate again, but who knows what might happen should one of those spheres broke? As for the whereabouts of the magic clock, well...that's a different story.	
		</Option>
	</Options>
</Configuration>